Watch out, shillers!
Is that FartyCoin’s army?
- No, It’s OurCoin’s community.
But hasn’t StanCoin’s infiltration
of their Telegram started?
You must flood them with FUD faster!
We’re running out of time!
But you said you had
this all under control...
StanCoin’s bot army was supposed
to wreck OurCoin’s group.
He claimed it would overtake
their Telegram!
Everyone except him knows
that’s pure fantasy.
I wonder if he even believes it himself.
- Why would he pretend at this point?
He’s got nothing left to lose.
I’m no longer buying your shit coins.
The OurCoin community made a breakthrough!
They seized our Telegram channels and reported them.
Now the authorities are banning our sock-puppet accounts!
They’re advancing from every angle—
Our offshore funds are getting flagged.
Regulators in the west have frozen
our stablecoin reserves and blacklisted withdrawals.
If StanCoin hits them with a final rug-pull,
we can still recover, right?
Farty Commander…
StanCoin…
StanCoin didn’t muster enough “degen” to infiltrate.
The Telegram infiltration…
never took place.
The following tokens remain here:
SolKitty, DogeSwap, PepeInu, and MemeChain.
That was an order!
StanCoin’s infiltration was an order!
How dare you ignore
my perfect scam blueprint?
Is this what we’ve come to?
They all lied to me—
the devs, the marketing shills, even the whales.
All these influencers are worthless:
No liquidity, no moral backbone.
I won’t accept that, we did everything…
Cowards, traitors, incompetent con-artists!
- Farty Commander, that’s outrageous!
They are the sludge
of the crypto world!
No sense of decency whatsoever.
They call themselves “pros” because
they spent years forging whitepapers…
…but all they really learned
was to steal code on GitHub.
For ages, those dreaded regulators
and on-chain detectives blocked my grand plans.
Every time, they messed up
just when victory was near.
I should have…
…liquidated all those worthless top brass,
like LUNA did in May 2022!
I never went to any “Crypto Academy.”
Yet I still dominated
half the meme-coin market!
Traitors—every one of them.
I’ve been double-crossed and hoodwinked
from the very first presale.
Such massive betrayal
of our once-glorious scam empire.
But these traitors will pay—
either in prison or monstrous fines!
They’ll drown
in their own compliance forms.
He is bluffing, our scams are not over.
All my directives
have been ignored.
How can I remain “Farty Commander”
under these circumstances?
It’s over.
Our grand rug-pull is finished.
If you think I’ll simply walk away
from this fiasco…
…you’re mistaken. I’d rather
burn my tokens than surrender.
Flood PumpFun and MoonShot
with fancy shit coins!
Farty Commander wouldn’t actually
destroy himself, would he?
SolDoge… ButtCoin…
Pack your wallets and ledgers. In one hour,
a private jet will whisk you away to a no-extradition paradise.
Everything is lost.
Completely lost.
You know I’ll stay here with you.
FartyCoin’s scam is all I have left.
Farty Commander, I’m staying too.
Now what?
Time to end this charade.
Should we just give up scamming?
Inconceivable!
The Farty Commander refuses to surrender.
No more capitulations—no 2022 references, ever!
But he doesn’t want to lead anymore.
He literally said:
“Flood PumpFun and MoonShot with fancy shits.”
No one can replace him.
He’s the one true master of meme scams.
He’s just confused.
He’ll bounce back.
Great. Then what’s the plan?
There’s no real “plan.”
He never intended to lose.
We owe him everything.
- That’s meaningless drivel.
We have to act now,
or we’ll be indicted next.
You only care about your own ass!
- Watch your words.
Damn it…
We’ll never get out unscathed.
It’s definitely over.
We should wait a bit.
Even the Farty Commander
no longer believes in a comeback.
HaukTuah says there’s a hidden network
that tunnels under the new KYC rules.
Why did you swear
you’d stay with her?
I don’t know.
Honestly.
It’s quiet now.
Let’s go take a walk.